http://www.childcaredepot.com/privacypolicy.html

Shopping Cart  |  Customer Account |  Wish List
(Mon-Fri 9am - 5pm ET)
HomeAbout UsFinancingOrdering InformationTerms and ConditionsPrivacy PolicyFAQsContactUsVideosBlog
Categories
JOIN OUR MAILING LIST!
Want to extend your dollars? We have Financing!
Privacy Policy
Personal Information:
Child Care Depot only collects personal information when you request our services and only uses the information collected to provide those services for you. If you choose to make a purchase, you will be asked to provide contact information (such as your name and shipping address) and financial information (such as your credit card number and expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to process your order. Child Care Depot handles all of this data with the utmost confidentiality.
Third Parties:
Any personal information provided will not be traded, rented, sold or otherwise shared with anyone outside of Child Care Depot or used for reasons beyond those contemplated in this statement. From time to time, we may engage third parties to process your information on our behalf; however, none of Child Care Depot affiliates (such as our credit card or finance company) have permission to retain, share, store or use personal information for any reason other than providing the requested service.
Security
To prevent unauthorized access, disclosure and improper use of your information, we have established appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial safeguards to protect the information we collect in accordance with our privacy policy. Our secure servers protect your information using advanced encryption techniques and firewall technology.
Home
© 2020 Child Care Depot
